Click here to display the menu of Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona [UAB Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona](https://www.uab.cat/web/universitat-autonoma-de-barcelona-1345467954774.html) [Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona](https://www.uab.cat/web/universitat-autonoma-de-barcelona-1345467954774.html)

Website search 

The UAB Promoting knowledge, encouraging innovation

* Data protection policy

Data protection Display navigation

Data protection

Data protection policy
======================

UAB Data Protection Policy
--------------------------

The Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona is committed to a policy on the protection of individuals' rights and freedoms regarding the processing of their personal data. For this reason, information on its students, academic staff, administrative and service staff, graduates, suppliers, clients and other persons associated with it is handled entirely as stipulated in law.

Personal data processing is carried out at the UAB with the consent of the data subjects, in order to perform contracts and agreements, defend the vital interests of data subjects or other persons, comply with legal obligations, exercise its competences and powers as a public institution, or further its own legitimate interests or those of third parties.

Personal data are only disclosed to third parties when this is permitted or mandatory in law.

The forms placed on the UAB website to collect personal data must include the relevant information-governance clauses, as stipulated in data protection regulations. In all cases, the UAB only processes personal data that are strictly necessary for specific, explicit and legitimate purposes. Additionally, it applies various technical and administrative measures to protect the personal data of those using its website.

This website contains up-to-date information on data protection law and the UAB's own regulations, procedures and standard forms in this area.

Browsing the UAB website does not necessarily imply that any personal data are collected from the visitor. However the UAB may place cookies on devices used to access the website in accordance with its policy on the use of cookies. The UAB only uses cookies to facilitate and personalise browsing. The data generated when browsing the UAB website are processed strictly for technical purposes by staff subject to the obligation of secrecy.

Web map
-------

Follow us on social networks
----------------------------

International recognition of excellence
---------------------------------------

With funding from
-----------------

About this website
------------------

We are a leading university providing quality teaching in a wide variety of courses that meet the needs of society and are adapted to the new models of the Europe of Knowledge. Our courses provide students with outstanding practical experience, helping them to be better prepared as they enter the professional world. UAB is internationally renowned for its quality and innovation in research.

Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona 2024
